You know, I'm so glad I never got involved with you.
I just would have ended up being some woman you had to get up out of bed and leave at 3 o'clock in the morning and go clean your AND irons.
And you don't even have a fireplace.
Not that I would know this.
Why are you getting so upset?
This is not about you.
Yes, it is.
You are a human affront to all women, and I am a woman.
Hey, I don't feel great about this, but I don't hear anyone complaining.
Of course not.
You're out the door too fast.
I think they have an OK time.
How do you know?
I mean, how do I know I know?
Because they...
Yes, because they... How do you know that they're really?
What are you saying?
That they fake orgasm?
It's possible.
Get out of here.
Why?
Most women at one time or another have faked it.
Well, they haven't faked it with me.
How do you know?
Because I... Oh.
Right.
That's right.
I forgot.
You're a man.
What does that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
It's just that all men are sure it never happened to them, and most women at one time or another have done it, so you do the math.
You don't think that I could tell a difference?
No.
Get out of here.
Oh.
Are you okay?
Oh, God.
Oh.
Oh, you're right there.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh.
I'll have what she's having.